{
    "id": "ecf2acf418be4294838bade8019c8afa",
    "title": "Present Perfect Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ........................................ to all the continents in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dfbd1e3281bf4e8cbb208c0be749bf28"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never ............................................ a ghost.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "seen",
                "see"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3517104b49284bd3b0096f8fa9399fcb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................................... experienced despair.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "08077b84e2814f4f96dc4e72057f0def"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .......................................... that movie.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has seen",
                "saw",
                "have seen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c9dc21a287bb49019b73addb08fef121"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .............................................. all the novels written by Mark Twain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am read",
                "have read",
                "had read"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d24329d048de445cb9682819db9e7b37"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ......................................... faced many setbacks in life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "76bba6661efd41aba72cc62dae0ceff5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................................. written a novel.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7acd2c946ac2451bbc3bbfb1304a009b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju ................................................. played cricket at the national level.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7db23eabaaec42c49ebf6e7d9bad56d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ........................................... seen her before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "01fdde3d44274ffcafb1472f85be23ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .............................................. that movie.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "watched",
                "have watched",
                "has watched"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9411293382234f459955a668d4933b0d"
        }
    ]
}